Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2015
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with video projection by Olivier Pasquet, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name CHANGE 7.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_342.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with video projection by Olivier Pasquet, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name SEND SEND SEND SLEE.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_343.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1026.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_344.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1027.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_345.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Saturday SLEE.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_346.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1028.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_347.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1029.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_348.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Slee Saturday_01.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_349.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1032.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_350.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1033.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_351.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1034.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_352.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Brad Lubman conductor m Heather Buck soprano, Ethan Herschenfeld bass.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_353.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal after the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1040.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_354.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal after the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1043.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_355.tif)
- Composer David Felder onstage with conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal after the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1045.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_356.tif)
- Composer David Felder onstage with conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal after the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1048.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_357.tif)
- Composer David Felder onstage with conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal after the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Ethan Herschenfeld bass, Heather Buck soprano, composer David Felder Irving Arditti concertmaster SEND.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_358.tif)
- Composer David Felder onstage with conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal after the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name composer David Felder Heather Buck sopranon Ethan Herschenfeld bass.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_359.tif)
- Composer Harvey Sollberger presenting a lecture at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Harvey Sollberger_2.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_360.tif)
- Composer Harvey Sollberger presenting a lecture at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Harvey Sollberger lecture.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_361.tif)
- Stefan Sanders conducting the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra in a rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Buffalo Philharmonic.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_362.tif)
- Composer David Felder checking his score of Six poems from Neruda's Alturas while Stefan Sanders conducts the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra in rehearsal at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1075.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_363.tif)
- Composer David Felder checking his score of Six poems from Neruda's Alturas while Stefan Sanders rehearses with the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1086.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_364.tif)
- Composer David Felder at the podium with conductor Stefan Sanders during a rehearsal of the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name composer David Felder with conductor Stefan Sanders.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_365.tif)
- Composer David Felder at the podium with conductor Stefan Sanders during a rehearsal of the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1094.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_366.tif)
- Composer David Felder at the podium with conductor Stefan Sanders during a rehearsal of the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1095.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_367.tif)
- Composer David Felder at the podium with conductor Stefan Sanders during a rehearsal of the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1099.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_368.tif)
- Composer David Felder at the podium with conductor Stefan Sanders during a rehearsal of the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1101.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_369.tif)
- Composer David Felder speaking at a June in Buffalo 2015 concert by the Buffalo Philharmonic Orchestra, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1104.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_370.tif)
- Stefan Sanders conducting the Buffalo Philharmonic in performance at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1136.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_371.tif)
- Stefan Sanders conducting the Buffalo Philharmonic in performance at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-07, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1137.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_372.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name SLEE SEND SEND.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_373.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name untitled_02.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_374.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name untitled_01.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_375.tif)
Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the Library's online catalog.
Subjects
June in Buffalo--Photographs; Composers--Photographs; Music festivals--New York (State)--Buffalo--Photographs; Musicians--Photographs
Genres
Digital photographs; Portrait photographs
Associated Material
Related Resources
Related Resources in the Music Library
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2000
Mus. Arc. 18
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2000 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2001
Mus. Arc. 19
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2001 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2002
Mus. Arc. 20
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2002 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2003
Mus. Arc. 21
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2003 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2004
Mus. Arc. 25
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2004 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2005
Mus. Arc. 27
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2005 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2006
Mus. Arc. 29
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2006 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2007
Mus. Arc. 38
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2007 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2008
Mus. Arc. 39
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2008 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2009
Mus. Arc. 50
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2009 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2010
Mus. Arc. 55
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2010 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2011
Mus. Arc. 56
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2011 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2012
Mus. Arc. 60
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2012 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2013
Mus. Arc. 66
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2013 June in Buffalo.
Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo 2014
Mus. Arc. 67
Finding aid for collection of photographs for 2014 June in Buffalo.
June in Buffalo Photograph Collection
A selection of images from the June in Buffalo festivals are available through University at Buffalo Libraries Digital Collections.